let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Who programmed the first computer game 'Spacewar!' in 1962?",
        answer: "A. Steave Russell",
        options: [
            "A. Steave Russell",
            "B. Konard Zuse",
            "C. Alan Emtage",
            "D. Tim Berners-Lee"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Who is known as the father of supercomputing?",
        answer: "D. Seymour Cray",
        options: [
            "A. David J. Brown",
            "B. Gene Amdahl",
            "C. Adam Dunkels",
            "D. Seymour Cray"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Who created the C programming Language?",
        answer: "B. Dennis Ritchie",
        options: [
            "A. Ken Thompson",
            "B. Dennis Ritchie",
            "C. Robin Milner",
            "D. Frieder Nake"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Who is known as the father of internet?",
        answer: "C. Vint Cerf",
        options: [
            "A. Alan Perlis",
            "B. Jean E. Sammet",
            "C. Vint Cerf",
            "D. Steve Lawrence"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which one is the first high level programming language?",
        answer: "C. FORTRAN",
        options: [
            "A. C",
            "B. COBOL",
            "C. FORTRAN",
            "D. C++"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "India's first Super Computer PARAM 8000 was installed in",
        answer: "B. 1991",
        options: [
            "A. 1990",
            "B. 1991",
            "C. 1992",
            "D. 1993"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Who developed Java Programming Language?",
        answer: "A. James A. Gosling",
        options: [
            "A. James A. Gosling",
            "B. Brendan Eich",
            "C. Bjarne Stroustrup",
            "D. Guido van Rossum"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which one is volatile memory in a computer system?",
        answer: "B. RAM",
        options: [
            "A. ROM",
            "B. RAM",
            "C. Hard Disk",
            "D. Floppy Disk"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "One Terabyte(1 TB) is equal to?",
        answer: "D. 1024 GB",
        options: [
            "A. 1000 GB",
            "B. 512 GB",
            "C. 1024 MB",
            "D. 1024 GB"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Who first developed QWERTY keyboard used in computers and phones?",
        answer: "C. Christopher Latham Sholes",
        options: [
            "A. James A. Gosling",
            "B. Win Ebbinkhuijsen",
            "C. Christopher Latham Sholes",
            "D. Shafi Goldwasser"
        ]
    }
]